mockuptree.com 2019-03-31

# Privacy Policy | Mockuptree

If you require any more information or have any questions about our privacy policy, please feel free to [contact us](https://mockuptree.com/privacy-policy/?xurl=http%3A%2F%2Fmockuptree.com%2Fcontact%2F).

At mockuptree.com, the privacy of our visitors is of extreme importance to us. This privacy policy document outlines the types of personal information is received and collected by mockuptree.com and how it is used.

 **Log Files**

Like many other Web sites, mockuptree.com makes use of log files. The information inside the log files includes internet protocol ( IP ) addresses, type of browser, Internet Service Provider ( ISP ), date/time stamp, referring/exit pages, and number of clicks to analyze trends, administer the site, track user’s movement around the site, and gather demographic information. IP addresses, and other such information are not linked to any information that is personally identifiable.

 **Cookies**

mockuptree.com does use cookies to store information about visitors preferences, record user-specific information on which pages the user access or visit, customize Web page content based on visitors browser type or other information that the visitor sends via their browser.

 **DoubleClick Cookie**

  * Google, as a third party vendor, uses cookies to serve ads on colorlib.com.
  * Google’s use of the DART cookie enables it to serve ads to users based on their visit to colorlib.com and other sites on the Internet.
  * Users may opt out of the use of the DART cookie by visiting the Google ad and content network privacy policy at the following URL – [http://www.google.com/policies/technologies/ads/](https://mockuptree.com/privacy-policy/?xurl=http%3A%2F%2Fwww.google.com%2Fpolicies%2Ftechnologies%2Fads%2F)

These third-party ad servers or ad networks use technology to the advertisements and links that appear on mockuptree.com send directly to your browsers. They automatically receive your IP address when this occurs. Other technologies ( such as cookies, JavaScript, or Web Beacons ) may also be used by the third-party ad networks to measure the effectiveness of their advertisements and / or to personalize the advertising content that you see.

mockuptree.com has no access to or control over these cookies that are used by third-party advertisers.

You should consult the respective privacy policies of these third-party ad servers for more detailed information on their practices as well as for instructions about how to opt-out of certain practices. mockuptree.com privacy policy does not apply to, and we cannot control the activities of, such other advertisers or web sites.

If you wish to disable cookies, you may do so through your individual browser options. More detailed information about cookie management with specific web browsers can be found at the browsers’ respective websites.

 **Third Party Content, Links, Associations and Purchases**

Links to Other Blogs, Webspace and/or Materials found on Mockuptree.com are provided solely as a courtesy to our visitors. Mockuptree.com has no control over the linked sites or the materials, information, goods or services available or contained on these linked sites. Thus, Mockuptree.com is not and shall not be held responsible for and does not endorse in any way the materials, information, goods or services available through such linked sites or any of the privacy or other practices of such linked sites.

Mockuptree.com does not warrant that any information found on the linked sites is complete or accurate or that any information or any links on those sites are free of rogue programming. If you decide to access any of the linked sites, you do so entirely at your own risk. Mockuptree.com also reserves the right to terminate any link at any time.

Mockuptree.com uses 301 redirects for some of its affiliate links, this means that while some of the “preview”, “download”, “demo” and other links may look like they are on the Mockuptree.com domain they are in fact external links to pages on other domains (our affiliate sites). These redirects are used for tracking purposes only, not to try and trick anyone into clicking them or to manipulate search engines.

As a user of Mockuptree.com you acknowledge that some links on this website will redirect you to other websites and the owner of Mockuptree.com will not be held liable for any problem or confusion cause from you clicking any of these links.

We reserve the right to change this policy at any time.
